.
THE HOUSE OF THE LAUGHING WINDOWS
My colors , my colors ...
They run hot in my veins ...
Sweet , my colors ...
so sweet ...
My colors are soft like the Fall ...
Hot like fresh blood ...
The liquid flows down my arms ...
They enter people 's minds ...
My colors ... they transcend me into darkness .
My colors take me so far away ... so far ...
My colors ... they flow through my veins ...
My colors , my colors , they erase everything else .
Purity , purity ... all my colors .
My colors will paint death clearly ...
Death .
I can tell , it 's coming !
Death is here . Finally . Purification ...
holding me at their mercy .
Purify me ... death ... ... my colors !
I 'm dying !
I 'm dying ! Purify me !
Purity ...
Good morning , I am Solmi .
Glad to meet you .
No , take hers , instead .
But no , women prefer to carry their own these days .
Anyway , welcome to our village .
Coppola !
I am the one who wrote to you at the academy ,
to restore the painting of St. Sebastian .
With this bad publicity from the papers ...
This is a tourist town and the thermal spring
is no longer enough to attract them .
Driver , to the church !
I 'm sure you 'll do a good job .
I hope so .
The original painter , Legnani , died at least 20 years ago
We can 't even name a street after him !
That 's why we called you .
Yes , I understand .
As soon as you finish his work , we 'll make it one of the
four main attractions of our region .
Next to our women . The water ,
... and silence !
Hey ! Are you drunk ?
Me , drunk ?
The pastor of the church is in charge of the painting .
He 's got the say there .
That 's where Legnani started it .
And we can 't move it , can we ?
This church was built , destroyed
and rebuilt , as far as I know .
If it wasn 't for me ,
it might not be here anymore .
Solmi says you came here before the war .
That 's correct .
Yes , this church used to be used by the SS .
There were even cadavers piled in here .
The priest had given up and left ,
only the walls were still standing .
So I rolled up my sleeves ...
until everything was cleaned up .
But then I discovered that this crap ...
was painted by the great Legnani .
He left it unfinished , it needs to be restored ...
so now I to have start all over .
Again ... no peace for me .
What an artist !
To illustrate death so well !
He understood everything !
Maybe , but with all the nice clean walls there is
Do we really need this rubbish ?
Poor guy !
He probably didn 't know that he was in a church !
They used to say he was crazy , maybe that 's true .
Hey , what are you doing ?
Are you starting now ?
No , I 'm just checking .
Okay , well , I 'm going to get something to eat .
I haven 't eaten anything since yesterday and I 'm starving .
Don 't take your work that seriously ...
cause here ... if you expect gratitude ...
You might wait a while !
She should stay in her room doing what she does !
Take this .
Yes , what is it ?
There 's a phone call for you .
It 's over there . Thank you .
Hello . Go away .
Pardon ?
You 're here for the painting ...
Who 's this ? Who 's on the phone ?
Don 't touch the painting !
Hey , you look great !
How are you ?
Hello , I 'm fine , thanks .
Today we have a special delice .
Here 's the cheese , want coffee ?
Yes , thank you .
You scared me at the hotel today !
Finally a new face in this hole ! Are you here for work ?
That 's correct , please , sit down .
Wait a second , this seat is already taken .
Antonio !
Will you thank me for this ? I 'm gonna sit over there .
What are you doing here ?
Who do you think recommended you ?
When I heard they needed a master , an expert
for old paintings , ... I thought of you .
How are you now ?
It 's all over !
I 'm well now . It was a nervous crisis , like I said before .
All I needed was a change of air .
And a breakup with Marcella ?
That bitch ?
No need for such discretion ...
Do you know who she is ?
Yes , she 's a teacher .
And she 's been fucked by everyone !
If you want to screw her hurry , before she gets thrown out !
Have you been to the church ? Yes , this morning .
Then you already saw the painting .
Yes , why ?
I 'd have preferred you 'd seen it with me .
You shouldn 't tell anybody this .
I think I discovered the strangest story ever .
That 's why I wanted them to call you .
Are you sure you 're well ?
I 'm okay .
I 'm fine , really .
But I 'll see you later .
I have to go now , I 'll get in touch .
Now he just takes two pills and he 's like new !
You have a nice room here , is it yours ?
No , I rent it .
Antonio says you 're a teacher , is that right ?
Yes , that 's right . Who do you teach ?
I teach kids , who do you think I teach ?
Oh , I don 't know .
How much sugar ? Not a lot .
Thank you . Watch out .
I always have tea when I want to make a good impression .
I hope I am !
Let me tell you something .
You have a sad face ...
I meant you seem nice !
A few years ago , no one would have dared to call me only nice !
With my kind of body !
If you feel lonely , come back .
You know the way .
I 'll be waiting for your visit .
Not in the morning , though , I 'm in school .
I 'll remember that .
For you to understand what I have to say
I must take you to a special place .
It 's a house with laughing windows .
That 's the story from yesterday ?
You used to have more wits ! ?
Do you know what they called Legnami here ?
Painter of Agony .
How jolly !
Yes , jolly , especially when
they started finding corpses !
Come here , Foresti !
Here you go , doctor .
Thanks , see you tomorrow .
Antonio , what about this story of agony ?
Hey , guys , good morning .
Doctor , that stuff you ordered for us , it arrived ?
Listen , save your money , I don 't need it after all .
There 'll be no more eels in this river ...
Hey , you know what ?
I 've got to start working too .
See you later !
Do you mind if I come along ?
Not at all . Sorry , I interrupted you .
What were you two talking about ?
Nothing much .
The painter and something about death .
You have a bizarre friend
and sometimes he doesn 't know what he 's talking about .
Somebody threatened me on the phone .
they tried to scare me , who might do this ?
One time there was this man , Zanotti ...
He molested women , until they arrested him .
Better to let it be . You can 't help it anyway !
Who put those flowers there ?
Well , I don 't know .
Why , don 't you like them ?
That 's it ! Let me go !
Please , you 're going to break everything !
Stop ! No more ! Stop this !
Get off my back !
Leave me alone , I tell you !
You know that , if I wanted to ... !
You know what I could do !
You 'll behave now ! Once and for always !
And you know what I mean ! Go home , go home , all right .
Scram !
Can I have a cigarette ?
It 's over .
Thank you , marshal .
Don 't mention it , Mr. Poppi . Thank you .
Good evening .
Sorry about the trouble .
This is the only restaurant in the village .
By the way , how do you find our food ?
Very good , I love it .
You are here for the Painting .
How 'd you know ?
Oh , everybody knows everything here .
And thanks to Solmi , things improved a lot here .
He 's done much for this village .
He 's a brave man .
Though not tall , he 's big .
He has led the village to unity and prosperity .
I 'm sure you find these pictures beautiful .
Like the one We have in the church .
These were painted by the same artist .
they are amazing . Oh , yes !
My wife , all these paintings belong to her .
But how she suffers !
She is very sick , She lives upstairs now .
This is her home .
She wanders about , she wal k s all o v er .
This is her favorite painting .
May I ? Yes .
It was Legnani 's first .
My wife is the model .
Quite startling the detail !
Joy from the Painter of Agony .
Poor guy , never a success with women .
Overpowered by them .
He never found a woman to be his model .
But one day he stripped down and started painting his body .
Hello , who 's this ?
One moment .
It 's for you .
Hello ?
Don 't mention my name .
I must speak with you .
I must tell you the rest of the horrible story .
I 'm at the hotel . In your room !
Someone pushed him from upstairs .
My god !
No , he 's dead !
It 's impossible !
Oh , God ! He took his own life ! I knew it !
Listen , I know how you must feel .
He was almost a friend .
Marshal , I 'm sure someone pushed him .
I saw a shadow .
Besides , he had no reason to commit suicide .
But there is no motive .
No reason for us to thin k
that someone killed him .
There is no evidence !
Soon you 'll understand ... this is no place for a young man .
He was a loner .
Unhappy , there is nothing to do here except drink .
the young women all left .
Your friend was alone , very alone .
In any case we sent the body to Ferrara for an Autopsy .
Good evening . Good evening .
Hello ?
Yes Sir , it 's for you .
Go away .
Leave the painting alone .
If you 're trying to scare me with phone calls ...
you 're not going to .
He loves me .
I 'm not leaving , understand ?
Excuse me , sir , one of our best clients
from out of town arrives tomorrow morning .
You 'll understand right ?
What are you saying ?
This man came to the hotel , there was no room for him .
So we gave him yours , we are very sorry , sir .
Do you like it ?
I still have some left from my fishing trip .
Want some ? They cook rats here .
You know , there are lots more around .
There best when boiled and still nice and hot .
What 's inside that box ?
What ? A secret .
Hey ! Let 's go !
Are we going or what ?
Hurry up !
It is spring and I am riding on a bike ...
the daughter of a scooter and a whore ...
killing hundred little bugs , as I pedal , merrily ...
What do you think ? Not bad ?
Are you coming or not ?
Hurry up !
You see , beautiful .
If you stay here you can do what you want .
Come on .
Here you go .
Who does it belong to ?
That 's not important .
You 'll see .
Come here .
This way .
It 's you ?
How come you didn 't eat ?
It 's all poisoned , you snake !
What did you do with the money I gave you ?
Thief !
If you don 't like what I bring , walk to a restaurant .
If I could only get up from this bed !
Who is this ?
Good morning .
He 's a kind man .
He 's gonna stay here a while until he finds a place .
It 's been a long time since I was visited by someone .
I am all by my self here .
The silence is unbearable .
Where is the man who took my room ?
Who do you mean ?
The new client .
There is no one .
The last tourist I saw here was a Nazi in the 40 's !
Who is it ?
Ah , it 's you .
I didn 't want to disturb you .
I thought you were sleeping .
Sleep ? Me ? Not quite .
How can a woman in so much pain sleep ?
Can I ask you a question ?
Do you hear noises at night ?
Noises ?
Yes . Last night ?
Yes .
Noises !
The only person you could bump into here is me
and I 'm not in that good of shape to be walking around .
I don 't think you 're in that bad of shape .
Come , young man .
Come next to me .
It 's been a long time since I 've talked with anyone sane .
It makes me happy that someone is concerned about me .
So , how 's the weather , is it nice out ?
Yes .
It 's a beautiful day .
You 'll come and see me often , right ?
Okay , see you later .
Goodbye , young man .
Is somebody there ?
My colors .
they are mine .
Let them run in my veins ...
they are soft , soft .
they are soft like Fall ...
Hot like fresh blood ...
the liquid flows down my arms ...
My colors , they transcend me into darkness ...
My colors take me into the yellow decay ...
My colors ... they flow through my veins ...
My colors in my veins ...
creating a brutal nobility ...
Oh God ... my God ...
my colors will paint death clearly ...
Death , Purity , Death .
Purification , holding me ... at their mercy .
My colors .
... dripping from their eyes .
Purity ...
Purity of death .
My colors ...
All my colors .
Purification , it flows in my veins .
Soft , hot , blood , death , the colors , the purity ,
they purify death through my veins . I am dying , I feel it !
Open up !
Is anyone home ?
Yes ?
Excuse me , I need to see the woman who lives here .
She 's no longer here .
Do you know what time it is ?
Excuse me .
She left three days ago , I 'm her replacement at school .
Come in , now that I 'm awake ...
Won 't you come in ?
I 'm sorry but I was sleeping , excuse the way I look .
Please , please , do come in .
Earlier I dreamt of being at the restaurant .
I was being served a huge portion of escargots .
Do you like them ?
I didn 't have the heart to kill them .
Interested ?
No , I don 't think I could eat them anyway .
What 's your name ?
Francesca .
Well , I 'm going back to bed .
I hope we see each other again .
Hey ! I put a live animal in your friend 's coffin
to keep him company .
Sir , I 'm concerned about the two women in the painting .
The killers of Saint Sebastian seem to be enjoying it .
Perhaps , too much , what do you think ?
I think we have the wrong idea .
The painter did not have the intention of depicting
the agony of the saint .
Everybody says the artist is a sensitive genius
but all he does is paint death ...
of a human without compassion .
Fishing is good around here , the fish are very hungry .
Have you noticed much change here over they ears ?
The village suffered after the war .
Everybody worked and rebuilt with courage and hope .
Tell me about the woman living at the house where I 'm staying .
The paralyzed woman ?
Yes .
I don 't see her much .
She 's the type who doesn 't invite me to her house .
She hasn 't left her bed in years .
People say she has a venereal disease .
But I wouldn 't know .
She doesn 't go to confession .
Was she friends with Legnani ?
Please don 't ruin my day with this kind of talk .
This kind of talk is even scaring away the fish .
Come on , let 's fish .
My colors .
Let them run in my veins
they are soft ...
soft. they are soft like Fall
Hot like fresh blood ...
the liquid flows down my arms . ...
My colors ...
they transcend me into darkness
Colors .
Purity .
Death . Purification , holding me
At their mercy .
My colors . Yellow .
I 'm dying !
My colors ...
blood ... in their eyes ...
Purity ...
What is this mumbo jumbo ?
I didn 't think you 'd come back .
I came anyway .
I was waiting for you .
I 've been here for two hours .
Curiosity made me play it , who is the man talking ?
I don 't know .
I 'm trying to find out .
Why do you live here ?
The priest suggested it .
Are you alone here ?
No , there 's an elderly woman upstairs .
She 's nailed to bed .
I can 't stop smoking , it calms me down .
Do you still want a cooking lesson ?
Escargots ?
No , something much better .
Come .
Do you know how to set a table ?
Yeah .
You 'll find everything you need in this drawer
and while you 're doing that , I 'll be in the kitchen .
Good .
I found a book in the old lady 's library ,
" Cooking For Romance . "
What did you think of the teacher I replaced ?
Did you like her ?
Pardon ? Do you have a lighter ?
Right there .
Did you make love with her ?
Your silence proves you did .
We stopped .
B. L. ?
Whose lighter is this ?
Do you know a painter named Legnani ?
No , it was a gift .
It 's a friend 's lighter .
The gloomy darkness is romantic .
Right ?
While eating this plate the lady and her knight
will feel love overpowering their souls .
Desire is strong .
Do you have a lot of luggage ?
One suitcase .
You could bring it over here .
Hey , what are you doing there ?
I s there where Legnani lived ?
Who ?
The painter , he did the painting at your church .
Can you drive me home ?
Yeah , hurry up .
Go ahead , sit in the front .
Must you go directly home ?
Would you like to get a drink ?
No , they won 't serve me .
they think I should be drinking fruit juice .
Like I can 't handle liquor !
Thank you .
The next one 's on me .
Yeah , if you want , but not today .
Why not ?
J ust tell me about Legnani . Right now ?
Yeah .
The painter ... he went to Brazil .
He went with his mom and two sisters
to find their fortune .
When they returned they were apparently wealthier
than before they left but mother died there .
they came back and built that little house .
Excuse me .
How did they live ?
What ? How did they live ?
He was poor .
He borrowed from everyone .
Even though they had a fortune , he had nothing .
His sisters controlled the money .
You know , I knew him . I was only seven .
She was dying , my mom was sick .
He came to draw her .
We called him the Painter of Agony .
He liked to paint people who were dying .
He wasn 't that crazy .
His sisters were devils .
By painting death he was trying to control nature ,
to confront death .
He was obsessed with death .
And the dying .
Could you recognize the sound of his voice ?
Could you recognize it ?
It 's the kind of voice you don 't forget .
He talked like a psycho !
Like a machine gun .
Then suddenly he would stop and start chanting .
Psycho !
He was really crazy because of his sisters .
Plug it in quick .
Yeah .
Okay , listen to this .
There 's nothing on this damn thing !
Did you touch it ?
Not since the other night .
Why ?
You touched it , huh ?
This tape was important to me , bitch .
What 's wrong ?
What 's wrong with you , I didn 't touch it !
I 'm sorry .
Excuse me .
I 'll be right back .
Francesca !
Coppola ?
Are you awake ?
I slept a little bit , but I had a bad dream .
I 'm sorry ...
I 'm scared , you know .
Me too .
But for me it 's different .
I 'm more afraid when I sleep .
There are a lot of things .
And they 're heavy !
Is everything packed ?
Yeah , just take it downstairs .
I ncredible .
Look , dear .
To verify the death experience of these models ,
to reproduce the very last moments of death ,
his sisters provided him with victims for his art .
His sisters ?
Why did he write this in third person like a researcher ?
To communicate with the dead mother of Legnani .
He talks of communion and sacrifice ,
human sacrifice ...
There 's a possibility that a man today can communicate
with the dead during the ritualistic painting .
That 's enough .
Stop it ! That 's enough !
Shut up !
I 'm begging , stop talking about it !
I 'm sorry , I can 't stand this place anymore .
I want to leave .
Rio de Janeiro .
From Rio de Janeiro .
What ?
What is it , tell me .
Probably the answer to all the craziness .
Who is it ?
I 'm sure it 's them ! Them ?
Listen , I can 't explain now , I really must leave .
Take me with you . No ! Stay here .
Get some rest , don 't open the door for anyone !
Beautiful flowers .
Beautiful flowers in the garden .
Beautiful flowers show my love for you my lord .
Beautiful flowers .
Beautiful flowers in my garden .
Only for you , my lord ?
Even today the sisters murdering through art .
What does this mean ?
Who 's there ? Ah , it 's you .
What are you doing here ?
It 's them ! It 's them , I tell you !
The painter 's sisters are the killers in the painting .
Look ! Take a look !
It 's true , they look the same .
Where did you find the picture ?
That 's not important , we are beginning to understand
what my friend had figured out before he died .
I don 't know why you 're so excited .
I feel possessed by this !
The painting .
The death of Antonio , it 's all too strange !
Yes , I believe you .
But I may not be on the right path .
I look at that cross and have serious doubts .
You 're scared too ?
Yes .
God forgot to give me courage , I 'll admit it .
Promise me you 'll stop this crusade .
Why ?
I 've seen many like you break down in the confessional .
Did you know the old lady at the house is dying ?
I was visiting her .
I gave her the last rites .
Let me see .
Oh yeah , it 's definitely them .
But tell me , where did you find this picture ,
it even surprises me that those two
would allow a picture to be taken at all .
I 've never seen one before .
This is quite an accomplishment .
Yeah , yeah , I know .
Well , what can you do ?
I think being a psycho is contagious .
When my wife was young she was beautiful .
From a big family .
She was infatuated with Legnani .
But he didn 't give her any attention .
He would only talk about what he did in that house
with his two sisters .
A sad little house close to the railroad tracks .
they moved there after the trip to Brazil .
And they brought back a beastly , savage religion .
Frightening .
One night , after he worked on the painting ,
Legnani decided to end it all .
Whenever he painted , he was in such frenzy .
Madness engulfed his soul .
He couldn 't separate reality from illusion in his work .
Blood and colors mixed together in his tortured brain .
His sisters pushed him and he finally stopped it all .
He forced them to watch as he covered his body with alcohol
and set himself on fire .
He ran into the wilderness .
His body was never found .
I told you , " Presumed dead . "
Why " presumed dead " ?
How many times must I repeat it ?
It says " presumed dead " , 4 th of J une , 1931 .
It doesn 't say " confirmed death " ,
it says " presumed " .
Do you understand ? Presumed !
Caught on fire , ran off , period .
Must I repeat it again ?
No , no , no .
Presumed dead .
So he could still be alive .
What !
With burns all over his body ,
such a man wouldn 't be too difficult to recognize !
I need three copies of these certificates by tomorrow .
Look them up in the master file .
How many times do I say it , this is not my job .
By the way , have you finished your work at the church ?
Yes , why ?
Because it 's been destroyed .
Can you tell me who did this ?
No .
I don 't know anything about it .
Someone , perhaps .
Maybe tonight !
You poor son of a bitch .
Maybe we should call a real specialist ?
Leave me alone , you degenerate .
Who 's there ?
Francesca ! France
Where are you ?
Oh , there you are .
Where were you ? It 's been over an hour .
I went to the city to make a phone call .
To whom , what happened ?
Nothing , nothing .
I called the home office in Rome .
I resigned from my teaching job .
You don 't want to stay here ?
No .
Stefano , you know I hate it here .
I hate the feeling I get in this house .
I want to run away .
Something bad is going to happen at any moment .
You said we would always be together .
You 're never here .
I feel so alone , and I 'm so scared .
U nderstand ?
Do you want to leave me ?
No , I won 't leave you .
There 's a train leaving tomorrow at 9 : 00 , let 's go .
Do you think we 'll get up early enough ?
Why didn 't you wake me ?
Are you going back to the church ?
Last night you promised we would leave together ,
why 'd you lie to me ?
I have a bit of time , I need to check something .
You can count on me .
I 'll give up everything for you , my love .
Bye .
Somebody there ? Somebody there ?
Good day . Good day .
I brought back the bike , it 's outside .
So , you 're leaving . Yeah , I 'm leaving .
Can you tell me something ? Yeah , sure .
Do you sell muriatic acid ? Yes , of course .
Need some ?
Who bought some recently ?
It was used to destroy the painting .
I sell it often to everybody in the village .
Who knows ?
You don 't write it down ?
Why ? I know everybody .
Everybody buys it , it 's used to clean .
I sell it to everybody .
Take me home , I need to pick up Francesca .
I beg your pardon , sir .
they abused me . Who ?
Them , all of them .
they were afraid I would talk !
She thought she could buy my silence
with a bit of booze .
But no more .
The last drink !
The sisters are still here .
they 're still alive .
Get closer .
Listen , I 'm the only one who has seen them in action ,
and it 's horrible , sick .
What do you mean ?
they tried to get me but I escaped .
When I was little I went to school with them .
Everybody thought I was stupid because I didn 't go to church ,
but I had a good reason .
I knew what was there , I knew the danger .
I don 't want to die there .
Others shut their eyes , ignored it .
But me , Coppola , is still alive !
And why is Coppola still alive ?
Because I ignore the others .
You think I 'm rotten ?
No . For real ?
Yeah .
Here the walls have ears .
My friend died because of that , right ?
I don 't know about your friend .
But I know you 're curious .
There 's a place where people like you ...
lose their heads !
Come ! Quick !
Come with me .
Is it you ?
It 's here .
This is a weird house .
Many people have disappeared here .
Why 'd you bring me here ?
I know they 're all here .
The missing people are all here .
Buried here .
There 's one here .
Once I thought I would end up in this hole too .
Stefano ?
You weren 't expecting me , were you ?
You take care of kids , right ?
So take care of me !
You aren 't scared of me , are you ?
Nobody 's scared of Lidio .
No ! You like me , don 't you ?
No !
There are many things I want !
Your skin drives me crazy !
I want you , don 't you want me ?
Give yourself to me !
Why resist .
I 'm stronger ! No !
Why are you fighting me , bitch !
Don 't scream .
You 'll wake up the old lady .
Shut up ! Don 't fight me !
I 'll take you to a house with odd windows .
Go get Francesca , I 'll wait for you .
Hurry up !
Stefano ! What ?
Don 't take long .
Francesca !
Francesca ! Are you ready ?
Francesca ! Are you there ?
Madame , have you seen
Francesca !
No !
Francesca .
Coppola ...
Yeah , it 's here .
Follow me , quick !
I know where they took her .
There , right there .
Dig !
Cigarette ?
What now , chief , continue ?
This probably surprises you but nothing 's here .
I 'm sure there 's something .
It 's true , I saw bones ... blood .
Who showed you that , who brought you here ?
Coppola , Mr. Solmi 's chauffeur .
Coppola ! Are you sure ?
Yes .
Okay , let 's go .
Coppola is a drunk idiot .
He made you look stupid , but you 're not the first .
Hey you !
Where did you find him ?
By the ravine near the church .
We 'll get him to you in a moment .
He 's heavy as a bull .
C 'mon , pull a little .
Pull !
There must be more alcohol than water in his body !
And what are these scars ?
I 've never seen them before .
they 're war injuries , he stepped on a mine .
God , he looks terrible !
Take the body to the morgue .
Come on , men .
Does anybody know where he was all day ?
No , he hasn 't been home for a week .
Oh well , check on it .
I don 't want you to go anywhere , stay with me .
Better yet , come to my office in the morning , understand ?
Sir ? I understand .
Come on .
Let 's go , I 'll take you to the hotel .
No , I have to find them first .
No , it 's not the right time , c 'mon , let 's go .
Yes ?
One moment .
You 're wanted on the telephone .
Who ? I don 't know .
Hello .
Hi , it 's me , Francesca .
Come , I 'm waiting for you at the house .
My love , I 'm scared .
Come , come now .
I 'm scared , scared .
I 'm waiting for you at home .
Quick ! Come now .
I 'm waiting , my love .
Hurry up !
You degenerate !
Aren 't you ashamed ?
Messed everything up !
Purification awaits .
Oh , come .
Come closer .
Follow me .
I 'm going to show you something .
See , it 's my little brother .
He will return to us soon .
We continue to bring models to him .
He lived through other people 's death .
Come .
Come , you are a friend of our little brother ,
aren 't you , sir ?
Can you hear his lovely voice .
Do you know how we keep him ?
Formaldehyde .
Libio brings us new formaldehyde every day .
But today Libio stopped to see your girlfriend he raped her .
He killed her , ruined her .
We had plans for her .
But he messed everything up .
We had to find a replacement .
Come .
Don 't be scared .
He looks so much like the man in the painting , doesn 't he ?
Bravo ! You didn 't miss !
Hold him .
He 's moving too much !
Stay here !
Think about our plan !
Wait ! Wait !
Get him from the other side !
Follow him !
He 's probably hiding in these bushes .
It 's useless to keep looking , he won 't get far .
Tomorrow we 'll come back and get his body .
We 'll get him , we 'll get him .
Please , I beg you .
Open up !
Solmi ! Solmi !
Hello , give me the police .
Open up ! Open up !
My God , Stefano , what happened ?
You 're my only hope .
I know what 's going on here , it 's them .
I know it 's them .
I know everything , I know everything !
Call a doctor , please .
The two sisters , the painter 's sisters .
It 's them , Legnani 's sisters are still alive ,
still alive !
they murder people ! they live !
they 're alive ! they 're still alive !
The sisters ! It 's them .
One of them owns the house !
The paraplegic ? Yes .
they 're alive , I swear .
The other one , I didn 't see her face .
That 's a nasty wound .
It would make a nice portrait .
Legnani would make a masterpiece out of it !
But you are
Beautiful flowers in the garden
show my love for you my lord .
Laura , come see , come see !